Barak Cohen

Javascript Developer

**** 052-5797294

■ baaraak0@gmail.com

github.com/baaraak

in linkedin.com/in/barak-cohen92/

About me

I'm passionate front end engineer with experience developing complex, high profile web applications collaborating with both small and large teams. I specialise in JavaScript, familiar with the agile environment and leveraging modern technologies such as React and Redux. Familiar with server-side languages like Node.js and PHP.

Experience

Amdocs

Software Engineer - React.js Developer (Nov 2017 - Aug 2019)

- Build complex front end applications from absolute scratch to a complete product.
- Experience with UI/UX design, optimize across various screen sizes and cross-browser.
- · Design and implement crucial business features.
- Working in agile methodology.

Techfinancials - Herzliya

Fullstack Developer - PHP, Wordpress, React.js (May 2016 - Oct 2017)

- Build responsive web and mobile web applications UI/UX from scratch.
- · Design and develop new business features.
- · Create new WordPress themes and plugins for customers.
- · Scrum master, control over agile process in the team.

Skills

- JavaScript
- Node.js
- ES6
- HTML
- CSS / SCSS / CSS-in-JS

- React
- Redux, Redux-thunk/saga/toolkit
- · Webpack, Babel, Gulp
- Testing
- Jenkis, Travis, CircleCI

- Responsive Design
- Mysql, MongdoDB
- Agile
- PHP
- Wordpress

Education

Full-stack web development.

HackerU College (2015 - May 2016)

- Full stack web development at HackerU college.
- PHP, MySQL, Laravel, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, SEO.

Languages

- Hebrew Fluent.
- English Good.